Hello friends, welcome
to another video of IndiaTech. Friends, today we
will discuss that if any
service is active on your bank account for which monthly charges are deducted
and you want to stop it or
want to see which services are engaged on your account for
which your monthly
charges are being deducted, then how to see it
and how to disable it, so let's start.
For this, first of all you have to
log in to your internet banking and
then go to customer services and
click on service request.
When your service request comes, then
you will select the bank account, which
is the first option and see, the
last option here is ECS NA
CA mandate cancellation, so all your
mandates which are
linked to your bank account will be visible in it, so you
will click on it, then it is asking for which
account number you want, so you will
select your account number from here
and see, I had taken a small case
of Basant Maheshwari, so see,
this amount is deducted from him and this is his URL number
etc.  So this is a mandate put on
my account for which I have to pay a
monthly charge. Now I
want to disable this service, so
how to disable it, if you have
multiple services, then you will select it, in this way
you will click on I agree and submit it,
after that an OTP will come on your mobile,
you will enter that OTP here
and submit it, then
you can see that your
request has been sent and whenever it gets
completed in a day, you can
come again and check, you will not see that service here,
so in this way you can stop any
mandate that is put on your savings
account, so that's all for today's
video, if you liked this video then you
can like it and
if you have any question related to it
then you can ask in the comment box,
thank you very much for watching